Guide to the Behind the Veil: Documenting African-American Life in the Jim Crow South Records, 1940-1997 and undated, bulk 1993-1997 RL.00170
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Electronic records - associated diskettes, 1991-1997; 1; 761 items
  - Disks, 1 (Box 7, Box 8)
    - Manuscript Excerpts - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0454)
    - Behind the Veil Summer 1995 Budget - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0455)
    - Behind the Veil Interim Report 11/96 (NEH.INT) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0456)
    - Advisory Board Letter - Advisory Board Letter 2 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0457)
    - Behind the Veil Summer 1996 Colloquium - Greta Nin - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0458)
    - JCP Summer 1995 II - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0459)
    - JCP Spring 1995 - Summer Planning - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0460)
    - JCP Spring 1994 - Summer Planning, Grants, Notes - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0461)
    - JCP Summer 1994 More - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0462)
    - JCP Undergraduate Course - Spring 1994 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0463)
    - JCP Fall 1995 General - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0464)
    - JCP Graduate Course - Letters, JCP Forms, Memos - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0465)
    - JCP Bibliography Project - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0466)
    - Behind the Veil Summer 1996 Colloquium - Jennifer Ritterhouse (Indexes) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0467)
    - Behind the Veil Summer 1996 Colloquium - Jennifer Ritterhouse - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0468)
    - Jim Crow Bibliography Summer 1996 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0469)
    - New Iberia Presentation (newib.pre) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0470)
    - Oral History Course Fall 1995 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0471)
    - Tribute to G. Hunter - Editor's Note, editors.html - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0472)
    - Jim Crow Bibliography Summer 1992 - jimcrowbib, jimcrowa.bib (alphabetized) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0473)
    - Behind the Veil 1993 and 1994 Database (Original) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0474)
    - Behind the Veil 1993 and 1994 Database (Duplicate A) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0475)
    - Behind the Veil 1993 and 1994 Database (Duplicate B) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0476)
    - Behind the Veil 1993 and 1994 Database (Duplicate C) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0477)
    - Behind the Veil Quick Reference Database, Database of Interviews in Excel - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0478)
    - Behind the Veil Biographical Database - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0479)
    - Behind the Veil 1994 Database - Copied 9.19.96 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0480)
    - Behind the Veil 1995 Database - Copied 9.19.96 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0481)
    - Behind the Veil 1993 Database - Copied 9.19.96 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0482)
    - Behind the Veil Photographic Archive Index (Duplicate) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0483)
    - Behind the Veil Image Archive Index - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0484)
    - Behind the Veil Photographic Archive Index - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0485)
    - Behind the Veil Scanned Images - 19-0865-029-IN - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0486)
    - Mendi Scanned Photos - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0487)
    - Behind the Veil Scanned Photos - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0488)
    - Behind the Veil Scanned Images - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0489)
    - Behind the Veil Scanned Image - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0490)
    - Behind the Veil Folders from Mac 9/29/99 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0491)
    - Behind the Veil Folders from Mac 9/29/99 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0492)
    - Behind the Veil Folders from Mac 9/29/99 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0493)
    - ProCite Bib File (bibtext from mac) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0494)
    - Bibliographies from Mac - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0495)
    - Bibliography Back Up Files - jimcrowa.bib - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0496)
    - Behind the Veil Notes Project Back Up - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0497)
    - HTML Pages - Web Site - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0498)
    - Jim Crow Backup - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0499)
    - American Communities Final Text Backup - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0500)
    - Behind the Veil Notes Project for Macintosh - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0501)
    - Behind the Veil Index Version 6/18/96 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0502)
    - Summer 2002 Miscelaneous Documents (Archive Links) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0503)
    - Behind the Veil Manuscript July 2000 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0504)
    - Behind the Veil Manuscript July 2000 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0505)
    - Behind the Veil Manuscript Word Copy 12/6/99 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0506)
    - Behind the Veil Folder text - Edited Transcripts - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0507)
    - Behind the Veil Text for Exhibit - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0508)
    - Behind the Veil Label Software and Templates - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0509)
    - Behind the Veil Transscipts from Arkansas State University - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0510)
    - Behind the Veil Shuttle Notes and Project Files - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0511)
    - Advisory Board for Behind the Veil Letters - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0512)
    - 1997 NEH disc - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0513)
    - 1997 NEH Budget Info - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0514)
    - Scan Disc Material (IBM) from Drive C 12/2/1997 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0515)
    - Website - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0516)
    - Behind the Veil on the World Wide Web newsletter documents - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0517)
    - Official Behind the Veil Mailing List, 5161 Mailing Label Template - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0518)
    - Inventory of Interviews - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0519)
    - Errors on Master Tapes - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0520)
    - Behind the Veil Work Forms for the Notes Project - ANP - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0521)
    - Jim Crow Project: Bibliography, Research Plan, Minutes - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0522)
    - JCP Comm. Disc - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0523)
    - Aminah N. Pilgrim - Invoice/Job Description - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0524)
    - JCP Box Inventory - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0525)
    - Behind the Veil - Greta Niu, LTRS, 1994-95 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0526)
    - Jim Crow Project: ASC II Files - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0527)
    - Walker, Luke - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0528)
    - NEH DOL - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0529)
    - Behind the Veil NEH Grant Write-Up - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0530)
    - Behind the Veil NEH Grant, August 1996 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0531)
    - New Bern, NC - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0532)
    - Charlotte - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0533)
    - Enfield, NC - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0534)
    - Memphis and Summerton Lists - a:\memphis, formatted - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0535)
    - Behind the Veil PC: Key Stats Relating to Behind the Veil Interviews, 1993 and 1994 Excel - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0536)
    - Community Stories - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0537)
    - Keisha - Rug Hooking - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0538)
    - Keisha's Excerpts - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0539)
    - Keisha's Behind the Veil Files - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0540)
    - Paul Ortiz: 19th Century US BTV.Art - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0541)
    - Paul Ortiz: Preface, American Communities - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0542)
    - Artie's Behind the Veil Notecards (Pro-Cite) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0543)
    - Artie's Behind the Veil - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0544)
    - Behind the Veil Newsletter (Artie's Dish) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0545)
    - Background Info - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0546)
    - Bookmaking Project Scan - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0547)
    - Chapter 1: Bitter Truths - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0548)
    - Chapter 4: Lessons Well Learned - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0549)
    - Card From the Heart - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0550)
    - ker1@acpubduke.edu - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0551)
    - Keri - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0552)
    - Nelda's Diskette - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0553)
    - Harriet Wade Letter - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0554)
    - Notes project (Mac) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0555)
    - Blair Murphy: 9 Articles (Pro-Cite) - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0556)
    - Jonora Jones' Pro-Cite Disk - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0557)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Johnson - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0558)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Davis - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0559)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Grant - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0560)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Smith - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0561)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Weathers - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0562)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Clem and Geo - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0563)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Brobson - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0564)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Brobson - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0565)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Brobson - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0566)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Butter - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0567)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Bbdf - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0568)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Art - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0569)
    - Behind the Veil Interview Transcript: Drelrann - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0570)
    - Taylor, J. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0571)
    - Taylor, J. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0572)
    - Ira Lee Jones? - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0573)
    - Homer Hill MS Interviews - Standardized - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0574)
    - Rosewood - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0575)
    - Jim Crow - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0576)
    - JimCrow.Fly - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0577)
    - JCP Stuff - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0578)
    - JCPBIB.DAT - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0579)
    - JCP - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0580)
    - Behind the Veil www - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0581)
    - Behind the Veil - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0582)
    - Behind the Veil - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0583)
    - Postcard Template; Roma.boy scan - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0584)
    - Letter - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0585)
    - Akzidenz Grotesque Grotesque - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0586)
    - Soho - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0587)
    - Soho II - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0588)
    - NSEP Brazil Gendered Domains - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0589)
    - docs - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0590)
    - Library Files Sept 89 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0591)
    - NEH.RES; Misc.AV; JCP Georgia Lynch Interview; UNC-WDIR (directions); CONTACTS.ENF; Response - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0592)
    - Free; Paradox; Taken off Computer 9 12/94 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0593)
    - Free disk; Paradox; Taken off Computer 10 12/94 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0594)
    - Duke Public Mac - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-FL3-0595)
    - Miscellaneous text, data, application, and email files - Optical disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-OP-0001)
    - Backup Job 1 - Disk 1 - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0001)
    - Backup: Behind the Veil Image Archive Database - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0002)
    - Pro-Cite Database Backup; Behind the Veil Book New Press - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0003)
    - Behind the Veil Interviews (Standardized) - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0004)
    - Behind the Veil Working Manuscript Files - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0005)
    - Behind the Veil Images - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0006)
    - Transcribed Interviews: 10/8/98, 3/3/99 - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0007)
    - Scanned Archive Images - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0008)
    - Behind the Veil Brochure - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0009)
    - 660-3656; Illustrator File 8.0 - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0010)
    - Behind the Veil Bibliographic Database - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0011)
    - Behind the Veil Biographical Database, Notecard Database, and Updatable Manuscript - ZIP disk, undated (Box 8, Disk RL00170-ZIP-0012)